eduvision.edu.pk 2013-11-25

# EduVision - About Us :: Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how http://www.eduvision.edu.pk uses and protects any information that you give http://www.eduvision.edu.pk when you use this website.

Http://www.eduvision.edu.pk is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Http://www.eduvision.edu.pk may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from June, 2012.

**What we collect  
**We may collect the following information:

Name and job title  
Contact information including email address  
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests  
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**What we do with the information we gather  
**We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

**Internal record keeping.  
**We may use the information to improve our products and services.  
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

**Security  
**We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies  
**A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Links to other websites  
**Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
**Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Children Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
**We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only  
**This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Controlling your personal information  
**You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

**Disclaimers /Terms and Conditions  
**  
Please also visit our Disclaimers section establishing the use and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.eduvision.edu.pk

Your Consent  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy  
**If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

Contacting Us  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Website: http://www.eduvision.edu.pk

Email:  [webmaster@eduvision.edu.pk](mailto:webmaster@eduvision.edu.pk)   
1239, St-58, G-11/2,
